Deep in the forest, morning begins. The trees wake together, roots woven as one.
Sunlight fills the canopy. Every tree shares the light, the shade, the life.
A gentle breeze drifts through the leaves. The forest breathes in peace.
Under the stars, the forest rests — safe, together, at peace.
Morning returns. The sun climbs high and pauses — a quiet moment before everything changes.
The sky darkens. Storm clouds gather. Lightning cracks through the air.
Rain begins to fall. The trees brace themselves, roots gripping tight.
The storm rages — but the forest holds firm, together.
As the storm passes, the forest drinks it in — turning flood into new life.
The sun returns. The forest stands taller — stronger for weathering it together.
A stranger arrives — an oil palm, all smiles and promises of prosperity.
But the smile is a mask. In an instant, it turns cold.
A document unfolds — a land title. The palm claims the forest's home.
With no home left, the native trees walk away — leaving everything behind.
Exhausted and displaced, they press on — searching for somewhere new to belong.
In their place: endless rows of identical palms. No shade. No shelter. Only silence.
Without the forest's canopy, the land bakes under a relentless sun.
The sky darkens again. But here, there's no canopy — the rain strikes bare earth.
With no roots to hold it, the ground gives way. A flash flood tears through.
When the water recedes, only ruin remains — cracked earth, fallen trees.
A few surviving palms return to the forest — heads bowed, seeking forgiveness.
This time, they're welcomed. Roots intertwine once more — proof that together, everyone thrives.